(Sheldon:)Well, this box only covers
my work through nursery school.
(Sheldon:)There's a good deal more to come.
I didn't really hit my academic stride...
(Sheldon:)...until I cut out that time-suck
known as playing outdoors.
You're gonna spend hours and hours
combing through all this stuff?
(Sheldon:)That's a good point.
My time is much too valuable.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I should find someone
to do it for me.
(Sheldon:)Someone with a rudimentary
understanding of science...
(Sheldon:)...but whose real talents lie
in menial labor.
- Not gonna happen.
- Yeah, well...
(Sheldon:)If I didn't think you could handle it,
I wouldn't be asking.
(Leonard:)If you want help, just hire a grad student.
- Maybe I could do it.
- Really.
(Sheldon:)You can assess the quality of my work?
Okay. Um, here.
I wrote this when I was 5 years old.
"A proof that algebraic topology...
...can never have a non-self-contradictory
set of abelian groups."
I'm just a blond monkey to you,
aren't I?
(Sheldon:)You said it, not me.